Okay. So, I I know the next the next
command is meant to be discuss phase,
but it says, "What do you want to
build?" And I just gonna I'm just going
to respond to that question because it
says back to where we were. Uh, so
please build the entire project.
Everything as described in planning/
plan.
Let's give it that command. That's what
we want. And uh we may have to do uh the
various uh GSD uh discussing phases and
so on. But got it. You want to build a
full trade trading workstation. Um
that's a solid foundation it says. Okay,
it's off. So uh we will um let it do its
thing. So this market backet and what
remains is data portfolio rest API chat
entire front end. A few things to
clarify. How polished does the front end
need to be for course demo? Um I uh what
do we think? I think we want something
really production quality. I I don't
think we want this to be like a demo
thing. I mean it is a demo, but we want
it to be really great. Production
quality. That's what we're going to say.
Uh for having the LLM chat, the plan
says Cerebras does. Should the LLM work
out of the box without an API mock mode?
Uh keys required. Um oh wait, works
without using mock real. Um
no, I'd say that that it should it
should need a key.
Docker. How should I build the Docker
file and stop start scripts or focus on
the app code? Include Docker for sure.
Submit answers. I love this. So, it's
really cool the way that it's
interactive and it comes back as the
distinct questions like that that we
that we answer. I think I have a clear
picture. Build a complete finding
platform end to end. Uh ready to create
project MD. Let's do that.
Okay.
So, it is this guided process. It's more
controlled on Rails, but still with this
idea that there's going to be a lot
happening on in parallel. So, I'm fine
for it to do that. I'm going to press
number two. There's going to be a few a
few I think approves as we go. Um, and I
will probably uh like make sensible
answers to questions. If there's a
really interesting one, I'll stop, but
otherwise, I will see you when we made
some more progress. Okay, it's been
about 20 minutes or something that this
has been chugging for and a lot has gone
on and it's now stopped and said V1
requirements uh covering database APIs,
front end, NLM chat, Docker and endtoend
tests. Uh does it look right? And this
is another is a good sign that that this
is somewhere in between the insanity of
of just using like teams that just go
off into the wild and a process that's
more on rails. And it's encouraging us
to look at a document called
requirements. And these documents are
all in a folder it's created called
planning. A bit confusing since we
called our own one planning already.
Let's go into planning. Here is
requirements.md
and open it up. And you'll see here are
the full requirements that it's got. And
we can just scan through it. You can see
it's got lots of uh bits and pieces that
it that it wants to to write and test.
This is super impressive. You can see
it's got all of these uh different IDs
for each part. It's given itself a a
checklist. Um lots of stuff going on,
things that are out of scope. The stuff
here that's putting in a V2 deferred to
future release, enhanced visualization,
social and discovery. Okay, sure. And
Terraform. Yeah, that that's all for the
future. Okay, excellent. I love it. I
say approve. Um, and it's a a great
opportunity for us to have come in and
read it and reviewed it. Off it goes.
It's now it's now uh proceeding. Um,
it's creating a road map as the next
step. So, it's not like you need to run
the commands that we looked at before
one by one. Uh, if you just interact
with it this way, then it will just
drive and it's off. So much is
happening. You can see that the main
context window is starting to fill up.
This is showing how much is being used
and it'll be interesting to see how it
handles it when that starts to get
tight. Anyways, again, I'm going to see
you in a minute. I'm going to to watch
over it and I'll come back if something
interesting happens. Okay, another key
moment. I'm being asked, does this road
map structure work for you? Here is the
road map. It suggested a proposed road
map in 10 phases. database foundation
portfolio trade execution watch list app
assembly LLM chat integration front-end
foundation watch list portfolio trading
chat interface packaging and testing
seems very sensible to me to me it seems
actually this is this is a better
approach than the the claude agents I I
like the way that the UI is being
deferred to a bit later that makes sense
to me I thought it was odd that claude
teams began with the UI uh and and yeah
the chat interface coming near the end
makes total sense to me starting with
the sort of nuts and bolts like this.
This this all seems really good. Uh
let's go with a one approve. Let's do
this. Okay, so now it's paused to say
that next up it's now it's got the uh
the project set up. It's ready now. I
will now have I thought maybe just
launch into to phase one, but it's up to
me to to run the command to kick off
either to discuss phase one or to go
ahead and plan phase one. And you know,
I think that it depends on the size and
the magnitude of your project. If you
wanted to discuss each of the phases, I
think that we should just go go right
ahead and go straight into planning.
Phase one, plan
phase
one. Let's just go straight into it and
get this show on the road. And so,
you'll notice that phase one has now
finished planning and it's ready for the
uh executing. And before it does that, I
just want to do a slash usage and just
see how much have we used now. Uh you
can see we're now at 18%. We've gone
from uh 8% to 18%. So it's definitely
it's quite something that that that uses
up a ton of space. Um it's already it
looks like about about almost double the
amount just to get to planning phase one
that the entire Claude teams used
before. So, it's definitely quite a hog
on tokens and it's quite slow, but this
has been going for a total of an hour
now. So, it's a very different
proposition to the team's structure that
we had before. Um, possibly I've I've
overboiled it by by making it into 10
phases like this. But anyway, I'm going
to press ahead. I'm going to execute
this phase and then unless there's
anything uh surprising that happens, I'm
just going to keep on going through and
see where we get to. Uh, this is this is
on yellow right now. So, I'm going to
also watch with interest as it deals
with the context. And I'll see you back
when we made some significant progress.
And that has now completed. It's now uh
it's completed the the execution of
phase one. You can see this context
looks really really full. And we can now
start planning phase two. Uh we we also
you could I could run the the verify
work, but that's for a sort of manual
step, which I'm not going to do. So, I'm
going to go straight ahead uh and do a a
GSD uh plan
phase
two. Uh and you can see that um the the
uh the the uh context is really looking
super full. I wonder I I don't know if
I'm allowed to say and three like that
if it can do them both together because
it says that that's also available. Can
run in parallel with phase 2. Let me try
that. And meanwhile, the context here is
very full. We'll see if this this
command works. We'll see what happened.
Uh it's thinking about that and uh
planning phases two and three in
parallel. It certainly can. All right.
So, I will let that go and I will see
you in a sec. Well, I have to confess I
have some slightly unexpected news for
you. The project has finished and as
you'll see here, it is 100% complete.
The thing that maybe is the fact that I
perhaps wasn't expecting, I don't know
if you was, is that it's actually 5
hours later for me that it is when I was
just here with you a second ago, 5
hours. This thing ground and ground. It
like thrashed over stuff. It was trying
to do a couple of things in parallel, a
bit like the using the the agent teams,
but basically it was very serial and
everything got checked and doublech
checked in an agonizing way. I have to
say that my initial reaction is it felt
overstoried. Perhaps I should have
condensed some of the phases on the road
map earlier. But for example, even
completing it, it's taken about half an
hour just to complete the project. It
marked it as complete. Then it had to
update its status to say that it was
complete. And as doing so, it had to
rerun the tests. But when it reran the
tests, it hit an issue even though the
test had already run successfully. And
so it went back and it thrashed and it
thrashed and discovered that in fact
there was some problem with the way it
was running the tests and in the end it
decided uh that it was finished. It says
churned for 1 minute but that's not
true. It churned for a lot longer than 1
minute. Uh so um in total if I now do
slash usage and we have a look at this
uh my current session usage at 24%
doesn't look too bad but that's cuz
we've gone past a day boundary and it
reset and then used 24%. This which used
to be about 9% has jumped up to 17% and
that had gone from 8 to 9 in the last
project. Basically we've consumed about
10 times the number of tokens and taken
about 10 times the length of time to do
it using GSD than using the the clawed
uh agent teams that we used before. And
so uh it was it was quite a palava but
it was very thorough very very
disciplined going through every single
step and doing tons of documentation.
There's a lot of documentation a lot of
code has been written an awful lot of
tests hundreds of tool calls. Um so so a
a big big thing went into this and I
could have left this going overnight and
and sort of woken up the next morning
and it would have been working for me
all through the night. So well not all
through the night but for five hours of
the night. Okay. So, at the end of all
of that, the big question is, is it
going to work first time just like it
worked for the other one? And is it
going to look different? Uh so I guess
we will find out uh after the